{
  "1a": {
    "question": "The _ was established in 1967, but has existed in some form since 1926.",
    "answer": "Federal Aviation Administration",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration"],
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "page": 0
  },
  "2a": {
    "question": "In 1934 the Aeronautics Branch was renamed the Bureau of Air Commerce.",
    "answer": true,
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "choices": [false, true]
  },
  "3a": {
    "question": "The FAA's mission is to provide the _, most _ aerospace system in the world.",
    "answer": "safest, efficient",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration", "safest, efficient"]
  },
  "4a": {
    "question": "The FAA Headquarters, located in DC, is comprised of multiple organizations and offices. These include: ",
    "answer": [
      "Airports",
      "ATO",
      "AFN",
      "Office of NextGen"
    ],
    "type": "multiple_select",
    "choices": [
      "Airports",
      "ATO",
      "AFN",
      "Office of NextGen",
      "DoT"
    ]
  },
  "5a": {
    "question": "The Office of the Deputy Assistant Administrator for Regions and Center Operations (ARC) reports to the FAA Administrator for the AFN and leads how many regional offices?",
    "answer": 9,
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration", 9]
  },
  "6a": {
    "question": "The ATO is responsible for ensuring the safety, efficiency, and security of air traffic operations across the entire NAS.",
    "answer": true,
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "choices": [false, true]
  },
  "7a": {
    "question": "The ATO is comprised of seven Service Units, including: ",
    "answer": [
      "Technical Operations",
      "Air Traffic Services"
    ],
    "type": "multiple_select",
    "page": "11",
    "choices": [
      "Technical Operations",
      "Air Traffic Services"
    ]
  },
  "8a": {
    "question": "AJT is one Service Unit of the ATO that provides: ",
    "answer": "Safe, secure, and efficient management for the NAS and international airspace assigned to U.S. control.",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "page": "12",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration", "Safe, secure, and efficient management for the NAS and international airspace assigned to U.S. control."]
  },
  "9a": {
    "question": "ATO ATC facilities are under one of three Service Areas, which include: ",
    "answer": [
      "Western",
      "Central",
      "Eastern"
    ],
    "choices": [
      "Western",
      "Central",
      "Eastern"
    ],
    "type": "multiple_select",
    "page": "13"
  },
  "10a": {
    "question": "As a controller, you will be at the _ of the FAA lines of authority.",
    "answer": "bottom",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "page": "15",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration", "bottom"]

  },
  "11a": {
    "question": "Visual Flight Rules (VFR) govern the procedures for conducting flight under visual conditions and are used to indicate: ",
    "answer": "weather conditions, type of flight plan",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "page": "18",
    "choices": ["Air Force", "NASA", "Yellowstone National Park", "Federal Aviation Administration", "weather conditions, type of flight plan"]
  },
  "12a": {
    "question": "ATC is responsible for separating a VFR flight from other traffic, terrain, and man-made objects on the ground.",
    "answer": false,
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "choices": [true, false],
    "page": "18"
  }
}
